Thank you for watching.
I wish I could show you now what I saw in my eyes that day.
I was just a child when my dream began
Looking back, I see a road that's been there for a long time
I couldn't do it right. I cried because I couldn't get a boyfriend.
In the beginning, there was such a thing, I remember
In front of me, it's always unfinished
There are nights when I get scared, but I have to go, because I can't find it
Because the only one who can give you the answer is you
I sang the song over and over without showing it to anyone
I sang it over and over and over again
I want to show you now... what I dreamed of that day...
The future, the future is shining right here
-The future is shining right here.
Hallo! This time, I'll be singing with Akari Takeuchi of Angeleum,
This time I'll be talking with Akari Takeuchi from Angeleum and Rin Hashishita from Angeleum.
I will be presenting this time with these two, so please bear with me until the end.
Now, this time, I'd like to introduce you to the "Halo! This time, we're going to be presenting the new single "Ai no Ai" by Angeleum, "Ai no Ai" by Angeleum,
This is the release of the new single "Ai no Kedamono" by Angeleum, a double A-side single of Alumnae and Alumnae.
Let's talk a little about this single.
Yes, I will.
First of all, it has the word "Ai no Kedamono" in the title,
The title of the song is "Ai no Kedamono," which means "Beasts of Love," and there are animal noises in the song,
There are animal noises in the song, and the animals are posed with their claws up,
There are animal noises in the song, poses with animal claws, and the lyrics "Gao",
The song is full of animal elements.
The dance in the interlude is done by the center,
Everyone is doing their best.
Everyone is working really hard, so please pay attention to that as well.
And for the alumni,
It's been a while since the staff gave me a touch,
The music video is really like that,
The music video really has that kind of atmosphere.
The music video really has that kind of feel to it,
I hope you will pay attention to the music video as well.
Also, my solo song "I gotta go! This song was written by Kohei Michishima,
This song was written by Kohei Michishima,
If people who have been supporting me since I was a child hear this song, they will not be able to listen to it without a handkerchief,
If those who have been supporting me since I was a little girl hear this song, they may not be able to listen to it without a handkerchief anymore,
We also shot a music video.
Isn't it beautiful? The director of the song said that when he thinks of Angstrom, he thinks of the ocean,
We used to go to the beach together a lot,
So I had them make it sound like we were all going to the beach together,
I'm very happy that he made the music video while considering the history of Ange, and what Ange is known for,
We are planning to release the music video as a single, so please look forward to the music video as well.
Please take a look at this video first.
Ending
People ask me what I like.
But in the end, it's not the choker
It's not the kind of love that makes you pull out myths and nemis.
We are a life for love
We are the girls who put our lives on the line
We are the target
Go!
Go! I can't be shy
We are the creatures that fall
Maybe you come away
Jump out of the car right now
Love me! We're so brave
What's the earth to begin with?
Check nick, today's the day
Feel my breath, feel my eyes on you
See, I'm already hooked
Love you! We're so easy
A fiery encounter is on the verge of heat
On the verge of a feverish heat
Hey, let me get out of your way
Feel how strong we really are
And the blade of love
You've got to be ready for this.
Someday, I'm sure, you won't be able to just hold my hand.
It's a bit of a love dialogue, isn't it?
You can't use tears as bait to lure me in.
It's the most basic of basics.
We are the aggressive world of love.
We are the attack world of love
We are the muevre that claws its way straight into the cosmos
If we are reciprocating, we are desperate to be intercepted
I can't allow that to happen.
I can't let that happen.
If you're using vague words to deceive and mislead
Let me tell you something.
I'll tell you.
I love you for being brave.
No matter what you say, the premise is always true
Even you, with your insanely sensitive nature
I'm sure you know what I'm talking about
I'll make love to you boldly, deceitfully
Primitive instincts, hesitant to put on
You're sweet on me, but you bite me hard
I'm absolutely crazy about you
car
ale
I love it, I love it, I love it, I love it
Let me love it, beep it, drop it now
I don't want to regret this. I don't want to melt it.
Now stop the clock, no survival strategy
I don't want to be licked
I want to love you, Rumor.I want to love you, Rumor.
On Earth to begin with, jackrabbits and cannibalism.
I can feel your breath. I can see your eyes.
♪ We're ready to spread our wings ♪
I want to love you, Rumor, we're bold, we're bold
I want to love you, my brave, bold, us
I'll protect you so much
I'll protect you so much, won't I?
Gently, gently, feel the strength, really feel the strength
You're a ball of love, aren't you?
Just be ready for anything.
Let's do our best tomorrow.
This episode of Halo! stay!
From here, we'd like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
Yes, I understand.
Well, here we go!
The spring tour of Big Love has just finished!
What do you think you accomplished on this tour?
Performance by 10 members
What was your bravest moment recently?
Fighting a spider.
It's been almost 4 years since I joined Angelem.
What do you think has changed the most since your debut?
Shyness
My relationship with Hayashi is that of a voice actor who fights a lot.
After I graduate, who will you be fighting with?
Manager.
Project is celebrating its 25th anniversary this year!
What is one song that Hayashi-chan can't miss?
Natsu Shogun
After I graduate, who will you be the voice actor to fight with? So that's what I was thinking,
Manager.
Manager, you're in trouble. Run away.
Run away right now.
I'll fight you.
I'm already fighting,
I'm already fighting, but from now on, I'd like to seriously face my manager and fight with him.
If you just take this out of context, it's a very nice thing to say.
Please don't take it seriously.
And please run away now, manager.
What should I do with the other one?
It's been almost four years since I joined Ajumu,
What do you think has changed the most since your debut? I'd like to ask you what you think has changed the most since your debut,
Shyness.
This is true that I am still a little shy with people I don't know, but I have gained in style and communication,
But I think I have become able to communicate with style.
I have conquered it to a large extent.
I think I have grown.
I have grown.
Keep up the good work.
I will do my best.
We'll leave the questions for Chisato Takei for after the VTR.
Hello! STE.
I wanted to love you, I couldn't love you
I won't kiss you Benchova.
I couldn't even tell you.
Pride Bright July 12, I'm Onser.
Next I would like to ask Mr. Takeuchi a question from me.
I'll do my best.
The photo book that was released last month
Roundabout
What can we see of you in this book?
It's a photo book that reminds me of myself from my debut to my latest work.
A new member has joined Angulum!
Please give a message to the new members.
Please continue to support us!
If you were to have a reunion for the new single, where would you like to go and what would you like to do?
Barbecue at the beach!
What is your third favorite Kanji character?
Dream
What is the No.1 title you would like to write down for your first song in Hello Project's history?
Natsu Shogun!
Oh!
Yes, I would like to write "Natsu Shogun" for the first time in my career.
That's right. We have a new member here, though,
A word to the new members.
Two new members, Yukiho and Hana Goto, have joined us on the lower board,
We haven't had a chance to do a lot of gutsy live performances together yet, but I would like to say a few words to the new members,
But I think their joining will bring about a chemical reaction in the future of Angulum,
I believe that I will be able to show you a different side of Angelem, a side that has never been seen in Angelem before,
I think that they are blowing a new wind in Angeleum little by little,
I hope you will continue to support us from now on,
I hope you will continue to support us. I chose these words.
It's very nice.
And the No.1 title I want to write on the first song of Hello!
Natsu Shogun.
This is already "Natsu Shogun," right? It's by Angelem, right?
There is a song called "Natsu Shogun,
It's already written in three kanji characters,
It's certainly cool.
And if it has the word "Shogun" in it, I would like to leave it in my book.
And I'm the one who wrote it,
I answered "Xia Shogun" earlier,
So I thought, "We are the same,
I thought, "Oh, I'm with you,
I knew it. I thought, "Oh, I just said that, so we are the same," and I thought, "Oh, I just said that.
Please listen to it.
So, Halo! I'll continue after this.
This is Natsuyaki Masashi.
Here we go. Hello Kitchen.Here we go. Hello Kitchen.
This time, we have a member here.
This is Yumi Okada from Tsuwaki Factory.
This is my first Hello Kitchen and I will do my best.
I look forward to working with you.
Please give my regards to Ms. Okada.
Yes, I'm Yumi Okada of Tsuwaki Factory. I am looking forward to working with you.
Well, sir, what would you like to cook today?
Yes, sir. We are going to make a cold shadow salad.
It feels like summer. It's cool.
It's getting hot, isn't it?
Yes, it is. Here are the ingredients for the cold shadow salad.
Yumi, do you usually cook?
Recently, I don't cook fried chicken or hamburgers.
I cook fried food and hamburgers with the help of my parents when I go home.
I used to be addicted to cooking for a while.
But recently I haven't done it at all.
I would like to take this opportunity to cook for myself again.
Please feel free to ask me if you have any questions.
I'm looking forward to hearing from you. I look forward to working with you.
Let's start cooking.
What should we do first, doctor?
First of all, I would like to cut the daikon into strips, or rather into thin strips.
I would like you to peel them first.
How is it? Can you peel it?
Have you ever used a peeler?
Yes, I have.
I can do it here.
Peel a wig?
Yes, I can.
That's great.
I've made radish stew before.
I'm nervous.
The camera...
That's right, usually.
You're supposed to push the daikon towards the cutter.
Do you like or dislike vegetables? Yumi.
Everything you can eat?
I used to.
But not anymore.
So you can eat everything today?
I just haven't eaten many seedlings.
The doctor said I could eat them.
I was wondering if you could.
It's a little habit-forming.
It's a challenge.
You're trying to get rid of the pungency?
And to make it crispy.
To make it crispy.
That's what you're thinking of.
That's right.
I see.
It's nice.
I have no problem with Yumi.
Really?
Yes!
It's done.
We're in it together.
It's like I've mastered the knife.
Yes, you're right.
Now let's cut the seedlings.
Cut them in half in the middle.
The seedlings smell amazing.
What do you think? How do they smell?
It's fine.
It's fresh.
First seedlings.
It's a bit of a challenge to see if they taste good today.
You put the seedlings in too?
You put them all in, didn't you?
Next...
Shall we try the mizuna?
About this much?
A little shorter.
About this much.
It's a little harder than you'd expect.
It's a little hard to eat when it's in the mouth, isn't it?
I see.
Yumi responds well, doesn't she?
She reacts to every bite.
It's fun to use a knife.
The first daikon you put in is cold, isn't it?
That's true.
It's crispy.
The sound is good, too.
The sound is good.
I'm getting on board.
And the kanwai.
We'll use one pack.
Let it rest and cut it around here.
Around here?
And a trivia.
If you put a little water in a dish and leave it here...
It will grow back in about 3 days.
It'll be like this again.
It grows in three days.
It grows.
It looks good, so it's fun to do.
It looks like a cactus.
It's an ornament.Ornaments.
This one's nice, too.
And then we'll mix it up a little bit, just to give it a little bit of a light mix.
Maybe cold.
It's cold.
It's cold, right?
Just a little bit. It's fine.
Let's split it in half and take out the core, shall we?
From the top.
That's fine.
This is just for decoration.
Let's slice it up a little bit.
Yes, sir.
Yes, that's good.
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Okay, it's done.
Okay, you can put it in here or something.
Last decoration.
It's like a topping.
Yes, it is.
Okay.
Let's move on to the next one. The next one is...
Okay, first of all...
You wrote you like ramen.
Yumi likes it? You like it? I love it.
I see... that's why there are noodles today.
It's a day shabu salad, but it's better with noodles.
I see. Thank you.
I love it.
I love it. Noodles for Yumi.
I hope she enjoys it.
But first, let's cut up the vegetables.
They're all nice and crunchy.
I'll put them in a colander.
Oh, it's done!
It's going. It's going to fall.
Is it okay? All of it.
Make sure you have a colander or something ready first.
Let's get started. You can start anytime.
We'll have to torture him with our hands.
Okay, we're ready to go.
Noodles are a summer favorite, aren't they?
I like cold noodles. Or pickled noodles.
Pickled noodles are good. I love pickled noodles.
Yes, mix it up a little.
I fell into the conversation.
I'll do it, sir.
Hot water's dangerous.
I'll turn off the heat.
Myabiz points! Myabiz points!
Myravizu Point. Just in time?
Just barely?
Miyabi's Point today.
We were about to lose entry.
Okay, here's a Miyabi's Point.
Never throw away boiled water.
That's a no-no. See you, doc.
Oh, no. There's still some water left.
That's good.
That was close. We almost lost a Miyabi's Point today.
Safe.
So, this is... boiled ramen noodles... boiled water...
Why don't you throw it out?
What's ramen noodles made of?
Wheat?
Wheat, right?
Wheat and water.
There's brine and stuff.
See this muddy color?
With this.
When you shabu-shabu...
It's really...
If you put potato starch on pork or meat
If you put potato starch or something on the meat
But I can't do it one piece at a time.
But we can't do it one by one.
There is a way to put potato starch on this side.
It's like an application of that.
Put sake and starch on this side.
Sake and?
Sugar
Put it in.
It makes the meat even more tender.
That's great!
Add alcohol and sugar
to make the meat smooth and tender.
I'm sure I
I always throw away the hot water after boiling the noodles.
I did.
That's right.
This time, I went so far as to not throw away the hot water.
I added sugar and sake.
I got to the part where the meat gets tender when I add sugar and sake.
I'll tell you the rest next time.
I hope you'll take a look at it again.
That's all for this time.
I never get tired of eating meat, no matter how much I eat
I know.I know.
Yum! Delicious!
I recently bought the ingredients to make a cold shabu salad.
How do you make it?
That's why you should take a look at this,
I'll make sure to see it through to completion.
So the next week, you'll do the cold shabu salad, too, right?
That's right.
So, you just wait until the next week,
And learn how to make it,
I decided to do it that way.
That's great.
I might just need the materials as soon as possible. First.
Vegetables, you know.
I already bought the ingredients.
Early.
So, about our recent cooking situation..,
I don't practice it these days,
I've been making carbonara, which wasn't a standard dish until a while ago,
Isn't it a standard dish? Carbonara?
It is not a standard dish.
If I were to eat it, it would be a classic,
But if you want to make it, it is quite difficult.
If you want to make it, it's a very difficult dish to make,
I think it is a very difficult dish to make,
I would like to make a classic dish,
Potatoes with meat and potatoes.
Why didn't it come up?
Potato stew.
I'd like to make a classic dish like "nikujaga" (meat and potato stew).
I'd like to try making some classic dishes, like meat and potatoes.
I have recently started practicing it again,
That's what I'm good at,
A mix of mixed peppers.
I'd like to make a meat and potato dish.
And chikuzen.
These three are too delicious to make by myself,
I make them because I want to eat them.
I'm going to make them by myself from now on,
I'm going to start cooking from now on,
After all, cooking for yourself is good for your health.
Let's work hard at cooking for ourselves.
I will teach you how to make meat and potatoes.
I'd really appreciate it.
What is it? I learned the recipe for nikujaga from Hello!
Like this.
Then it's definitely delicious.
It's definitely delicious.
Then, let's give it a try.
Hello! Ste.
Join us for the next episode of "Halo! Sta.
Now, on June 21, we are going to perform at Yokohama Arena for Angelem's concert 2023 Big Love.
Akari Takeuchi Final Live
Angelem with love will be held at Yokohama Arena on June 21.
Okay, I would like to talk to Ms. Takeuchi from here.
Yes, there's only a week left until graduation.
Wow, that was quick.
It's early.
How do you feel now?
I really don't feel it, to the point of being surprised.
That's true, isn't it? I don't feel it yet.
I remember the other day, when Momona Kasahara was graduating.
Momona was there and I was there, and the two of us were together when Momona was the last.
I was with her and I was with her. stage together when Momona graduated.
Momona probably said the same thing.
I thought it was so last minute, but I didn't really feel it until the day of the show.
I really don't know how I'm going to feel until the day of the show.
I really can't feel it.
I can't feel it.
But I think this is probably because Mr. Takeuchi is really cheerful as he has always been.
I haven't become a new beauty yet.
There are a lot of things called "the last XX.
I feel like it's the last to that point.
It seems like you're still going to be around forever.
That's why I've been doing this kind of thing at live shows.
I've been going to Osaka and Nagoya for a long time.
I've been going to Osaka and Nagoya since I was a member of Halo Pro Egg.
I've been going to the last Osaka show and the last Nagoya show for almost 15 years.
I've been going for almost 15 years.
I don't feel like it's my last time
I'm troubled.
It's so true.
But I'm really looking forward to being at Yokohama Arena.
I'm really looking forward to being at Yokohama Arena.
That's part of it.
Hallo! sta.
Love you, promising us!
To begin with, the earth is a place of the weak and the strong.
Feel the good use of the earth.
Angulum Ai no Kedamono Now on sale
I love you I'm sorry I doubted you
I love you, I love you, I love you so much I'm going to cut it off, Seven Eleven
Halo! Ste.
So, what's the best memory you have of the past four years that you spent with me?
Well, I'd have to say my favorite memory of Rin Rin is hanging out with her backstage.
Well, yes.
Whenever we had a lot of free time, like at a concert, she would always bring a card game with her.
I would always bring my card game.
I brought mine and Rin-chan brought hers.
We'd play for hours, and we'd play Fruits Basket for about 3 hours.
There were times when it was just me, Rin-chan, and Shion Tanaka.There was even a time when it was just me, Rin and Shion Tanaka.
We played backstage all the time, so I only have memories of playing with Rin.
We played all the time.
We really played all the time.
Sometimes the members change.
But this is the only place that doesn't change.
We were there from the beginning to the end.
I think it was a lot of fun.
I hope we can play again.
Yeah, I'll go out with you again.
Then please do so.
I'll come visit you at the school.
You're welcome to come over.
Okay.
I'll bring my card game.
You're more than welcome.
Okay, I'll be there.
Finally, do you have a message for your fans who are looking forward to the live show?
I know there's only a week left...
I'm going through a lot of emotions.
I feel like I'm graduating.
And also, as it's the first time for Angstrom
This will be the first time for me to perform in an arena by myself.
I also feel that we've finally made it this far.
I also feel that this is the culmination of all 10 of us
I think we will be able to show the culmination of the 10 of us at the Yokohama Arena,
I think we will be able to show the culmination of the 10 of us at the Yokohama Arena, and that's really what we have been doing every year for the past 12 years, singing and dancing,
I can't even imagine what it will be like to sing and dance as we have done every year for the past 12 years, but it will be over after this show,
I really want to make this the best concert I can,
I really want to make this the best concert ever,
I would like to express my gratitude to all of you who have supported us throughout the years, and I hope that you will join me in witnessing this event.
The other day, we announced that we have a new member,
A new member will join our group.
So today, I would like you all to meet the two of them,
May I call them now?
So, let's have them come out right away. New members, please!
Congratulations!
Let's begin with self-introductions.
I've decided to join Angelem!
Born in Okayama Prefecture
From Okayama Prefecture
I'm Yukiho Shimoita, a 16-year-old high school sophomore from Okayama Prefecture.
My member color is hot pink.
That's beautiful.
Yes, so, we have a member's color,
Yes, I see.
Kiyo-chan, do you have any enthusiasm?
First of all, thank you for choosing hot pink.
Everyone is so kind.
Yes, they are.
I'm glad.
You can call us Yukio-chan "Yupyon".
Yupyon.
Call me Yupyon.
I'll say it with everyone.
Yup, yup, yup!
Great!
How's it going? You happy?
Hey, that's right.
I made them cry.
I'm so happy.
Chan-chan.
Wait, wait.
Neither of us is a wreck anymore.
Well, let's take a break.
I'll ask you later how you're feeling. After you calm down.
Hana-chan, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Are you having an emotional hard time today?
Can I introduce you?
Yo!
I'm going to join Angulum as well!
Whew!
Hang in there, hang in there!
I'm Hana Goto, a 15-year-old junior high school student from Saitama Prefecture.
Nice to meet you... Oh, yeah.
What are the member colors?
Member color is,
It's simple.
Congratulations.
Nice to meet you.
Good for you.
Cute.
Wait, wait.
Isn't it too cute? This space.
It's so cute.
You happy?
Hey, Hana-chan.
Hana-chan, you call me Hananachan, right?
I call you Hananachan.
Hananana.
Isn't she cute?
I call her Hananana.
Let's go, everyone.
Ready?
Oh, my gosh!
I'm so happy.
So, Mikyao-chan, can you see your breath now?
Senyuki's doing her best.Senyuki will do his best.
I hope to catch up with my seniors as soon as possible,
I will do my best as a member of Angelem from now on,
So please give me your support.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you.
You are so cute.
As a member of Angelem, I will do my best to show my personality,
I will do my best to give a performance that will bring smiles to the faces of the audience and many people.
Thank you very much for your support.
So, these two will be joining us from now on.
That's right. I'll stop crying when I lean back.
Cry, cry, cry.
I want you to take a picture for sure, manager.
Are you taking pictures?
That's amazing.
So, I would like to say thank you very much to the two new members who will be joining us in the future,
I look forward to working with you all.
Thank you very much.
Now, I have one more announcement,
I will be graduating soon,
I would like to make an announcement about the new organization after my graduation,
After I graduate, the new leader will be...,
Ue-chan!
The new leader after my graduation will be Ue-chan!
I can't stop crying. I can't stop crying.
Then, are you waiting for my enthusiasm or something? See you.
It'll be the two of us.
That's right. I'd like to take over your leadership and grow Angeleum even more brightly, energetically, positively, and more positively.
And, I know many of you are surprised to hear that I am your leader,
I talked with Ms. Sasaki and Mr. Kawamura and we decided on it,
I am the leader, but I would like everyone to support each other and grow together,
I would like to continue to ask for your support.
So, these two have joined us,
And from June 22, Ue-chan will be the new leader,
Please support us from now on.
Cam will continue to be the sub-leader,
I look forward to your continued support.
I will support you all. Thank you very much for your support.
I hope that all of you will work together to create a wonderful group and a new, strongest Angstrom,
I will be just as vocal as you all from now on, and together we will make Angeleum more exciting,
I hope you will all join me,
I hope you will all join me and be a part of my group. Sta.
This is a special edition of "Halo! Sta.
It's time to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
Today, Angulum's new single
Ai no Kedamono Alumni has been released today.
All three songs are good, so I hope many people will listen to them.
And the single V I have to go will be released on July 12.
It will have a music video in it,
It will be released after my graduation,
Please check it out if you like.
On August 13, I will be performing at the Rockin Japan Festival 2023.
August 13th is the last day of Rockin Japan,
We are also very nervous, but we will do our best.
And finally, next week on June 21, we will be performing at Yokohama Arena for the Angelem Concert 2023 Big Love!
Akari Takeuchi Final Live! Angulum kara Ai wo Motto" (With Love from Angulum) will be held at Yokohama Arena next week on June 21.
As I mentioned a little while ago,
It will be the culmination of the 10 of us, and the first arena for Angulum,
It will also be my last live,
I'm sure there will be a lot of emotions,
I am sure I will have a lot of emotions, but I just want to enjoy the show,
I hope you can enjoy the show with me.
I hope you will enjoy watching it with me.
This will be the last time I, Akari Takeuchi, will be the MC for Halo! Stage for the last time.
That's right. I'm going to be the last MC for Halo! I've been doing it since the very beginning when I was doing it by myself.
I've been doing it since I was a solo MC,
At that time, I was not allowed to look at the script,
So it was so hard that I couldn't finish the recording in an hour or two,
But now I have very good memories of it,
At that time, we were still S/mileage,
I was still Smileage at that time, and I didn't have junior members yet,
Now I'm having a lot of fun MCing with all kinds of junior members,
From now on, I'll be looking forward to this "Halo! I hope I can continue to enjoy the show as a viewer,
I hope you will continue to support me in the future.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again as a viewer of Halo!
I would like to see Rin-chan having sushi with the new members someday,
Rin-chan will be the leader of the group, for example,
I would like to see Rin-chan having sushi at the new member's house when she welcomes the new member,
I'm really looking forward to seeing it on the "Halo! I'm really looking forward to seeing Rin-chan eating sushi at the new member's house when she becomes the leader and welcomes the new member,
Please lead Angstrom until then.
I will do my best.
I'm looking forward to seeing her eating Soushi at her child's house on the stage. Project members will be appearing more and more on the channel.
Project members. New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
This time, I was joined by Akari Takeuchi from Angeleum and Rin Hashizoko from Angeleum.
Good bye.
Thank you very much.
Please subscribe to our channel.